

Details

Address

32/12, Flat No - 30, Siddhatek Apt., Ambegaon BK. Pune-46 Pune, 411046 India

Phone

+91 80872 83418

Email

swapnilborate80@gmail.com

Date of birth

25-07-1991

Skills

HTML5

Bootstrap

CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

Angular 2+

Node.js

PHP

MySQL

MongoDB

Hobbies

Reading. Listening Music.

Travelling.

Languages

English

• • • •

Hindi

• • • •

Marathi

• • • •

Swapnil Borate

Front End Software Engineer

Profile

Creative, Passionate Front-End software engineer with 5 years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Specializes in using jQuery and Angular versions to build AI, IoT Platforms, and e-commerce, ERP, Health care applications.

Employment

Software Developer, Heaptrace Technology Pvt. Ltd.

Feb 2016 − May 2017 Pune

Front End Web Developer, Truelytics eComm Pvt. Ltd.

Software Engineer, Straviso India Pvt. Ltd.

Jul 2018 − Aug 2019 Pune

Software Engineer, Delmon Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

Aug 2019 − Present Pune

Education

Savitribai Phule Pune University, Masters Of Computer Science

Savitribai Phule Pune University, Bachelor Of Computer Science

Jul 2008 − Jul 2012 Pune

Projects

cLink & Trending Chat

Front End - HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Typescript, Bootstrap 4, Angular 7, Websocket **Back End** - Java, Spring Boot, REST API, Websocket.

Database - MySql 5. **Description** – Trending Chat is a web application and group chatting platform like web what's up. Logged In user can chat assigned group. User can also send important messages in red, green, yellow etc. color. User gets notification when user away from tab or browser. User can send attachments, images with captions and delete it.

Emcarta

Front End - HTML 5, Angular Material Design, Angular JS 1.5, CSS 3, SASS, Node JS, Gulp , Bower, Google Map API, FIR 2 API Back End - GoLang, REST API.

Database - MySql 5 Description - Emcarta (heart) is the organization who can manages all over hospitality. Application have three roles base authentication i.e. admin, providers (doctors), patient.

The data send in standard format i.e. FHIR (Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources) API. All API is available in FHIR. The reason behind the FHIR, provider can interchange data to another provider, organization. The Patient , Provider locate on map his current location. Patient can view the nearest provider, organization.